<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Company News on Divest Vanderbilt</title>
    <link>https://divestvanderbilt.com/categories/company-news/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Company News on Divest Vanderbilt</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Copyright &amp;copy; 2020 [Divest Vanderbilt](https://www.instagram.com/dores_divest_/?hl=en) All Rights Reserved</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 23 Aug 2021 11:07:10 +0600</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://divestvanderbilt.com/categories/company-news/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Founder’s Walk interrupted by Dores Divest demonstration</title>
      <link>https://divestvanderbilt.com/blog/chancellor_speech/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Aug 2021 11:07:10 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://divestvanderbilt.com/blog/chancellor_speech/</guid>
      <description>Dores Divest held a demonstration during Chancellor Daniel Diermeier’s speech at Founder’s Walk on Aug. 22 as their first protest of the 2021-22 school year. The group’s mission is for Vanderbilt to divest from fossil fuels.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Members of VSG, Dores Divest, DivestVU meet with administrators to discuss fossil fuel divestment</title>
      <link>https://divestvanderbilt.com/blog/admin/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jul 2021 11:07:10 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://divestvanderbilt.com/blog/admin/</guid>
      <description>On June 16, several members of VSG, Dores Divest and DivestVU met with Anders Hall, vice chancellor for investments and chief investment officer, and Eric Kopstain, vice chancellor for administration, to discuss the movement for Vanderbilt to divest from fossil fuels.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Divestment Activists win $1000 Climate Hub Award</title>
      <link>https://divestvanderbilt.com/blog/climate_hub/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 May 2021 11:07:10 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://divestvanderbilt.com/blog/climate_hub/</guid>
      <description>The Climate Hub Awards recognize undergraduate and graduate students and student teams who have completed exceptional projects on any subject in climate science and relationships between climate and society. The Climate Hub is an arm of the Climate and Society Grand Challenge.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dores Divest hosts Earth Day ‘oil spill’ demonstration in front of Library Lawn</title>
      <link>https://divestvanderbilt.com/blog/oil_spill/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Apr 2021 11:07:10 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://divestvanderbilt.com/blog/oil_spill/</guid>
      <description>Members of Dores Divest, student volunteers and around 40 student spectators gathered around the Harold Stirling Vanderbilt statue in front of Library lawn at 1:30 p.m. CDT for an “Earth Day Oil Spill” demonstration.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dores Divest Protest Vanderbilt Institute for Energy and Environment Closing</title>
      <link>https://divestvanderbilt.com/blog/viee/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Mar 2021 11:07:10 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://divestvanderbilt.com/blog/viee/</guid>
      <description>Students from Dores Divest met late in the night Sunday, Mar. 14, to post flyers in prominent areas around campus in response to a Vanderbilt Hustler article announcing that the Vanderbilt Institute for Energy and Environment (VIEE) would be permanently closing on June 30.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DivestVU, Dores Divest hold an over 30-person protest at Kirkland Hall</title>
      <link>https://divestvanderbilt.com/blog/23protest/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Feb 2021 11:07:10 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://divestvanderbilt.com/blog/23protest/</guid>
      <description>DivestVU and Dores Divest held an approximately 30-person protest today from 2:15 to 3 p.m. CST. The protestors marched from Library Lawn to Kirkland Circle in support of divestment of the university endowment from fossil fuels.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GUEST EDITORIAL: Vanderbilt, it’s time to divest from fossil fuels</title>
      <link>https://divestvanderbilt.com/blog/time_opinion/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Oct 2020 11:07:10 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://divestvanderbilt.com/blog/time_opinion/</guid>
      <description>Broadway—10 feet underwater. Nissan Stadium—an Olympic swimming pool. Islands of cars in parking lot oceans. This isn’t the Nashville of a distant climate projection but rather the Nashville of 2010. Ten years ago, landlocked Davidson county experienced catastrophic flooding.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
