<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Company News on Divest Vanderbilt</title>
    <link>https://divestvanderbilt.com/categories/company-news/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Company News on Divest Vanderbilt</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Copyright &amp;copy; 2020 [Divest Vanderbilt](https://www.instagram.com/dores_divest_/?hl=en) All Rights Reserved</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 16 Feb 2022 11:08:00 +0600</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://divestvanderbilt.com/categories/company-news/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>PRESS RELEASE: Dores Divest, peer universities file legal complaints against fossil fuel investments</title>
      <link>https://divestvanderbilt.com/blog/ag_complaint/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Feb 2022 11:08:00 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://divestvanderbilt.com/blog/ag_complaint/</guid>
      <description>National Coverage  Washington Post Guardian Reuters Grist PoliticoPro CommonDreams EcoWatch Bizjounrals Energy News Network  Local News  Vanderbilt Hustler The Nashville Scene   Complaints claim failure to divest violates the Uniform Prudent Management of Institutional Funds Act For years, students around the country have argued that their universities’ fossil fuel investments are immoral.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PRESS RELEASE: Dores Divest’s Statement on Chancellor Diermeier’s Conflict of Interest</title>
      <link>https://divestvanderbilt.com/blog/coi/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Jan 2022 11:07:10 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://divestvanderbilt.com/blog/coi/</guid>
      <description>Above: Chancellor Daniel Diermeier advises fossil fuel executives from ROSEN Oil Group and TC Energy Natural Gas Company during a panel titled “Managing Perceptions” at the 2020 International Pipeline Conference. Screenshot obtained from IPC 2020 Highlight Video.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>‘Of course:’ Al Gore endorses Vanderbilt divesting from fossil fuels</title>
      <link>https://divestvanderbilt.com/blog/gore/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Dec 2021 11:07:10 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://divestvanderbilt.com/blog/gore/</guid>
      <description>On Dec. 1, former Vice President Al Gore—who was once enrolled in Vanderbilt’s Divinity School and later enrolled in the Law School—explicitly endorsed Vanderbilt’s divestment from fossil fuels. He was invited on campus to speak at the Unity and American Democracy class about the connections between the climate crisis and issues in democracy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dores Divest protests outside L.A. Jackson alumni reception</title>
      <link>https://divestvanderbilt.com/blog/alumni_protest/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Oct 2021 11:07:10 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://divestvanderbilt.com/blog/alumni_protest/</guid>
      <description>Dores Divest staged a protest outside of an alumni reception—which featured Chancellor Daniel Diermeier—at the L.A. Jackson Bar and Restaurant in The Gulch on Oct. 19. This protest comes in the wake of the group’s Aug.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dores Divest hold Sept. 10 protest at Wyatt Center</title>
      <link>https://divestvanderbilt.com/blog/wyatt/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Sep 2021 11:07:10 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://divestvanderbilt.com/blog/wyatt/</guid>
      <description>On Sept. 10 at 4 p.m. CDT, students and community members gathered on the steps of Wyatt Center for Dores Divest’s protest advocating for Vanderbilt to divest from fossil fuels. 100 students signed up to attend the event, per Miguel Moravec, graduate student leader of Dores Divest.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Founder’s Walk interrupted by Dores Divest demonstration</title>
      <link>https://divestvanderbilt.com/blog/chancellor_speech/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Aug 2021 11:07:10 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://divestvanderbilt.com/blog/chancellor_speech/</guid>
      <description>Dores Divest held a demonstration during Chancellor Daniel Diermeier’s speech at Founder’s Walk on Aug. 22 as their first protest of the 2021-22 school year. The group’s mission is for Vanderbilt to divest from fossil fuels.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Waverly, TN flood affects Vanderbilt community</title>
      <link>https://divestvanderbilt.com/blog/relief/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Aug 2021 11:07:10 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://divestvanderbilt.com/blog/relief/</guid>
      <description>On Aug. 21, severe storms and 17 inches of rain in Waverly, TN resulted in a deadly flash flood that claimed the lives of at least 21 people, the youngest being seven-month-old twins.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Members of VSG, Dores Divest, DivestVU meet with administrators to discuss fossil fuel divestment</title>
      <link>https://divestvanderbilt.com/blog/admin/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jul 2021 11:07:10 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://divestvanderbilt.com/blog/admin/</guid>
      <description>On June 16, several members of VSG, Dores Divest and DivestVU met with Anders Hall, vice chancellor for investments and chief investment officer, and Eric Kopstain, vice chancellor for administration, to discuss the movement for Vanderbilt to divest from fossil fuels.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Divestment Activists win $1000 Climate Hub Award</title>
      <link>https://divestvanderbilt.com/blog/climate_hub/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 May 2021 11:07:10 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://divestvanderbilt.com/blog/climate_hub/</guid>
      <description>The Climate Hub Awards recognize undergraduate and graduate students and student teams who have completed exceptional projects on any subject in climate science and relationships between climate and society. The Climate Hub is an arm of the Climate and Society Grand Challenge.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dores Divest hosts Earth Day ‘oil spill’ demonstration in front of Library Lawn</title>
      <link>https://divestvanderbilt.com/blog/oil_spill/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Apr 2021 11:07:10 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://divestvanderbilt.com/blog/oil_spill/</guid>
      <description>Members of Dores Divest, student volunteers and around 40 student spectators gathered around the Harold Stirling Vanderbilt statue in front of Library lawn at 1:30 p.m. CDT for an “Earth Day Oil Spill” demonstration.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dores Divest Protest Vanderbilt Institute for Energy and Environment Closing</title>
      <link>https://divestvanderbilt.com/blog/viee/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Mar 2021 11:07:10 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://divestvanderbilt.com/blog/viee/</guid>
      <description>Students from Dores Divest met late in the night Sunday, Mar. 14, to post flyers in prominent areas around campus in response to a Vanderbilt Hustler article announcing that the Vanderbilt Institute for Energy and Environment (VIEE) would be permanently closing on June 30.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DivestVU, Dores Divest hold an over 30-person protest at Kirkland Hall</title>
      <link>https://divestvanderbilt.com/blog/23protest/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Feb 2021 11:07:10 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://divestvanderbilt.com/blog/23protest/</guid>
      <description>DivestVU and Dores Divest held an approximately 30-person protest today from 2:15 to 3 p.m. CST. The protestors marched from Library Lawn to Kirkland Circle in support of divestment of the university endowment from fossil fuels.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GUEST EDITORIAL: Vanderbilt, it’s time to divest from fossil fuels</title>
      <link>https://divestvanderbilt.com/blog/time_opinion/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Oct 2020 11:07:10 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://divestvanderbilt.com/blog/time_opinion/</guid>
      <description>Broadway—10 feet underwater. Nissan Stadium—an Olympic swimming pool. Islands of cars in parking lot oceans. This isn’t the Nashville of a distant climate projection but rather the Nashville of 2010. Ten years ago, landlocked Davidson county experienced catastrophic flooding.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Case For Fossil Fuel Divestment</title>
      <link>https://divestvanderbilt.com/blog/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Oct 2020 11:07:10 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://divestvanderbilt.com/blog/about/</guid>
      <description>A decade ago, noted environmentalist Bill McKibben had a radical-sounding idea. To save the planet, we needed to “revoke the social license of the fossil fuel industry.” His comprehensive vision of fossil fuel divestment would require financial institutions and civil society to stand shoulder-to-shoulder.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Alumni: How to get involved</title>
      <link>https://divestvanderbilt.com/blog/alumni/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Oct 2020 11:07:10 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://divestvanderbilt.com/blog/alumni/</guid>
      <description>Vanderbilt&amp;rsquo;s most famous former student, Al Gore, called for fossil fuel divestment at Harvard University, which ultimately divested in 2021. We need the leadership of more alums like Al and yourself to help turn the tide on fossil fuels at Vandy!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Faculty: How to get involved</title>
      <link>https://divestvanderbilt.com/blog/faculty/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Oct 2020 11:07:10 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://divestvanderbilt.com/blog/faculty/</guid>
      <description>Pictured above, Professor Curtis Baysinger (VUMC) joined student activists at our Sept 10th protest to advocate for fossil fuel divestment and a national carbon tax. We need the leadership of more Professors like Dr.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Students: How to get involved</title>
      <link>https://divestvanderbilt.com/blog/students/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Oct 2020 11:07:10 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://divestvanderbilt.com/blog/students/</guid>
      <description>Want to help turn the tide on fossil fuels at Vandy? Here are 3 ways you can get involved:  Sign the community petition  Hundreds of other students have already signed, but we need your name and email as well!</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
